Mauricio Alejandro Vidales Garcia

Phone:

9992 43 76 25

Email:

vidalesgarciamauricio@gmail.com

Profile

Mechatronic engineer with experience in the automotive sector analyzing technical documentation, defining manufacturing processes and creating work instructions. Also in the development of software projects for process control, using the C# to create windows forms and SQL for design, create and use relational databases. Continuous search for new experiences and knowledge.

Employment History

Ksquare University - Salesforce Associate Software Engineer (February 2021 - Present)

- Four Months of intensive training to become a Salesforce Developer 1 Certified.

LEONI Wiring Systems Yucatan – Team Leader Board Design and Product Engineer (April 2018 – February 2021)

- Two Months of capacitation in Serbia as part of the core team of engineering.
- Creation of layouts using AutoCAD, for the construction of automotive harness from the customer technical drawing.
- Implementation and control of technical changes of the product, production processes and internal documentation.

LEONI Wiring Systems Yucatan – Software Project Merge Rack (January 2019 – April 2020)

 Program developed with C# on Visual Studio to create Windows forms application, and SQL for the database. For the control in real time of subassemblies not finished, using a bar code scanner for identify each subassembly.

LEONI Wiring Systems Yucatan – Software Project Calculator of PDC subassemblies (May - July 2019)

- Program carried out for the control of production of modules, according to the customer daily demand. Using C# and writing csv files as output.

Professional practices - Plenum Group (August 2017 – March 2018)

- Programming of embedded system with PSOC4 and XBEEs using language C, for the prediction of forest fires in the state of Yucatán. PCB design using Eagle software.

Education

Facultad de Ingeniería Universidad Autónoma de Yucatán (August 2012 – December 2017)
Graduated by EGEL exam, Ceneval Award, qualification of outstanding performance testimonial.

Skills

- Ability to understand problems and propose solutions
- Adaptable and easy to work in a team.
- Ease and desire to learn new technologies.
- Project Management

Languages

Spanish - Native language

English – Medium, fluent in conversations and writing documents.

Hobbies

Scouting and Camping. Boy Scout since 6 years old until 25 years old.